<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>bomber.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxBomberxx</name>
  <description>
    <p>
      Bomber is a single player arcade game. The player is invading various cities in a plane that is decreasing in height.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Bomber is en Enkelspeler-Speelhallenspeel. De Speler griept en Reeg Steder mit en Fleger an, dat jümmers wieder daal kummt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Bomber is een arcade spel voor een enkele speler. De speler is bezoekt verschillende steden in een vliegtuig dat dat steeds lager gaat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Bomber to gra arcade dla jednego gracza. Gracz najeżdża różne miasta na płaszczyźnie, która obniża się na wysokości.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Bomber — аркадна гра для одного гравця. Гравець бомбардує з літака міста, висота будинків у яких поступово зростає.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxBomber is a single player arcade game. The player is invading various cities in a plane that is decreasing in height.xx</p>
    <p>
      The goal of the game is to destroy all the buildings and advance to the next level. Each level gets a bit harder by increasing
      the speed of the plane and the height of the buildings.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Dat Speel is, Du rietst all Hüüs daal un kummst so na de nakamen Speelstoop. Elkeen Stoop is sworer; de Fleger fliggt gauer un de Hüüs sünd höger.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het doel van het spel is om alle gebouwen te vernietigen en verder te gaan naar het volgende niveau. Elk niveau wordt een beetje moeilijker door de snelheid van het vliegtuig te verhogen en de hoogte van de gebouwen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Celem gry jest zniszczenie wszystkich budynków i przejście do następnego poziomu. Każdy poziom staje się coraz trudniejszy poprzez zwiększanie szybkości płaszczyzny i wysokości budynków.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Метою гри є зруйнувати всі будинки і перейти на наступний рівень. З кожним рівнем гра стає складнішою, оскільки зростає швидкість літака і висота будинків.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe goal of the game is to destroy all the buildings and advance to the next level. Each level gets a bit harder by increasing the speed of the plane and the height of the buildings.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=bomber</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdegames/bomber/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/bomber.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <developer_name>The KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Komunita KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nds">De KDE-Meenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">De KDE gemeenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Społeczność KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Спільнота KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxThe KDE Communityxx</developer_name>
  <provides>
    <binary>bomber</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
