<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.bomber.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Bonbaketaria</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Bombar</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Bombowiec</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Бомбардер</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Bombarder</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Бомбардер</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Bombarder</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Bombacı</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxBomberxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Bomber</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">戰鬥機_Bomber</name>
  <summary>Arcade Bombing Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc arcade de bombardeig</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc arcade de bombardeig</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Arkádová bombardovací hra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Arkade-bombespil</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Fliegerbomben-Spiel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Ηλεκτρονικό παιχνίδι βομβαρδισμού</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Arcade Bombing Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego recreativo de bombardeo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Põnev pommitamisemäng</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Arkupeko bonbardaketa jokoa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Arkadipommituspeli</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Jeu d'arcade de bombardement</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Xogo arcade de bombardeo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Bombázós játék</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Permainan Pengeboman Gedung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gioco di bombardamento arcade</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">아케이드 폭격 게임</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Arcade-bommenwerpspel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Bombespel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Gra w upuszczanie bomb</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Jogo de Arcada de Bombardeamento</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogo de bombardeiro tipo arcade</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Аркадная игра «Bomber»</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Arkádová bombardovacia hra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Arkadna igra bombardiranja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Аркадна бомбашка игра</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Arkadna bombaška igra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Аркадна бомбашка игра</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Arkadna bombaška igra</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Spelhallsbombspel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Bombalama Macera Oyunu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Аркадна гра у бомбометання</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxArcade Bombing Gamexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">街机风格的轰炸游戏</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">大型遊戲機的戰鬥機遊戲</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Bomber is a single player arcade game. The player is invading various cities in a plane that is decreasing in height.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Bomber je arkadna igra za jednog igrača. Igrač napada razne gradove avionom koji smanjuje visinu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Bomber és un joc arcade per a un sol jugador. El jugador està envaint diverses ciutats en un avió que va disminuint en alçada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Bomber és un joc arcade per a un sol jugador. El jugador està envaint diverses ciutats en un avió que va disminuint en alçària.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Bomber je arkádová hra pro jednoho hráče. Hráč napadá různá města, v letadle které klesá ve výšce.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Bomber er et arkadespil for en enkelt spiller. Spilleren invaderer forskellige byer i et fly ved lavere og lavere højde.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Bomber ist ein Arcade-Spiel für einen Spieler, bei dem unterschiedliche und in der Höhe steigende Städte mit einem Flugzeug angegriffen werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Bomber είναι ένα ηλεκτρονικό παιχνίδι για έναν παίκτη. Ο παίκτης εισβάλλει σε διάφορες πόλεις με ένα μαχητικό το οποίο χάνει ύψος.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Bomber is a single player arcade game. The player is invading various cities in a plane that is decreasing in height.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Bomber es un juego recreativo para un único jugador. El jugador está invadiendo diversas ciudades en un avión que cada vez vuela más bajo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Bomber on üksikmängija arkaadmäng. Mängija peab ründama erinevaid linnu lennukil, mis laskub aina madalamale.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Bonbaketaria jokalari bakarreko arkupeko joko bat da. Jokalariak inbasio erasoa egiten die hainbat hiriri altueran jaisten ari den hegazkin batean.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Bomber on yhden pelaajan pelihallipeli, jossa pelaaja hyökkää kaupunkeihin lentokoneella, jonka korkeus vähenee vähitellen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Bomber est un jeu d'arcade pour un seul joueur. Le joueur doit envahir des villes depuis un avion dont l'altitude décroît.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Bomber é un xogo arcade para un único xogador, que montado nun avión invadirá varias cidades mentres o aparello vai reducindo a súa altitude.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A Bomber egy egyjátékos arcade játék. A játékos különböző városokat igáz le egy repülővel, ami folyamatosan veszít magasságából.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Bomber adalah sebuah permainan arkade pemain tunggal. Pemain adalah menyerang berbagai kota dalam sebuah pesawat yang menjatuhkan bom dari ketinggian.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Bomber è un semplice gioco arcade per un solo giocatore. Questi deve invadere delle città in una pianura inclinata.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Bomber는 단일 플레이어 아케이드 게임입니다. 플레이어는 계속 하강하는 비행기를 타고 도시를 침략합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Bomber is en Enkelspeler-Speelhallenspeel. De Speler griept en Reeg Steder mit en Fleger an, dat jümmers wieder daal kummt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Bomber is een arcade spel voor een enkele speler. De speler bezoekt verschillende steden in een vliegtuig dat dat steeds lager gaat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Bombar er eit arkadespel for éin spelar. Målet er å bomba byar med eit bombefly som stadig flyr lågare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Bombowiec to gra zręcznościowa dla jednego gracza. Gracz najeżdża różne miasta na płaszczyźnie, która obniża się na wysokości.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Bomber é um jogo simples para um jogador. O jogador está a invadir diversas cidades com um avião que vai reduzindo a sua altitude.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Bomber é um jogo tipo arcade para um único jogador. O jogador está invadindo várias cidades com um avião que vai descendo em altitude.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Bomber — аркадная игра для одного игрока. Игрок атакует различные города с бомбардировщика, и они уменьшаются по высоте.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Bomber je arkádová hra pre jedného hráča. Hráč napáda rôzne mestá v lietadle, ktoré klesá.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Bomber je enoigralska arkadna igra. Igralec napada raznolika mesta z letalom, ki se sčasoma spušča.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Бомбардер је аркадна игра за једног играча. Нападајте градове авионом којем опада висина.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Bombarder je arkadna igra za jednog igrača. Napadajte gradove avionom kojem opada visina.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Бомбардер је аркадна игра за једног играча. Нападајте градове авионом којем опада висина.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Bombarder je arkadna igra za jednog igrača. Napadajte gradove avionom kojem opada visina.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Bomber är ett spelhallsspel för en ensam spelare. Spelaren invaderar olika städer i ett flygplan som flyger på allt lägre höjd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Bombacı tek oyunculu bir makine oyunudur. Oyuncu yüksekliği azalan bir uçakla çeşitli şehirleri istila eder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Bomber — аркадна гра для одного гравця. Гравець бомбардує з літака міста, висота будинків у яких поступово зростає.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxBomber is a single player arcade game. The player is invading various cities in a plane that is decreasing in height.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Bomber 是一个街机风格的单人游戏。玩家将乘坐一架高度正在徐徐降低的轰炸机入侵不同城市的领空。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Bomber 是個大型單玩家遊戲。玩家要侵略多個城市，由高到低。</p>
    <p>
      The goal of the game is to destroy all the buildings and advance to the next level. Each level gets a bit harder by increasing
      the speed of the plane and the height of the buildings.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Cilj igre je da uništite sve zgrade da bi prešli na sljedeći nivo. Svaki nivo postaje malo teži povećanjem brzine aviona i visine zgrade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'objectiu del joc és destruir tots els edificis i avançar al següent nivell. Cada nivell es torna més difícil, incrementant la velocitat de l'avió i l'alçada dels edificis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'objectiu del joc és destruir tots els edificis i avançar al següent nivell. Cada nivell es torna més difícil, incrementant la velocitat de l'avió i l'alçària dels edificis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Cíl hry je zničit všechny budovy a postoupit do další úrovně. Každá úroveň bude trochu těžší kvůli zvýšení rychlosti letadla a výšky budov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Målet med spillet er at ødelægge alle bygningerne og komme videre til næste niveau. Hvert niveau bliver lidt sværere ved at flyets hastighed og bygningernes højde øges.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Das Spielziel ist die Zerstörung aller Gebäude und der damit verbundene Aufstieg in die nächste Ebene. Die Ebenen werden durch die zunehmende Geschwindigkeit der Flugzeuge und Höhe der Gebäude immer schwieriger.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο στόχος του παιχνιδιού είναι να καταστραφούν όλα τα κτήρια και η προώθηση στο επόμενο επίπεδο. Σε κάθε επίπεδο η δυσκολία αυξάνεται με την αύξηση της ταχύτητας του μαχητικού και του ύψους των κτηρίων.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The goal of the game is to destroy all the buildings and advance to the next level. Each level gets a bit harder by increasing the speed of the plane and the height of the buildings.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El objetivo del juego consiste en destruir todos los edificios para avanzar hasta el siguiente nivel. Cada nivel se va haciendo más difícil al aumentarse la velocidad del avión y la altura de los edificios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Mängu eesmärk on hävitada kõik ehitised ja jõuda järgmisele tasemele. Iga tase muutub aina raskemaks: suureneb lennuki kiirus ning kasvab ehitiste kõrgus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Jokoaren helburua eraikin guztiak suntsitu eta hurrengo mailara aurreratzea da. Maila bakoitza zailxeagoa bilakatzen da hegazkinaren abiadura eta eraikinen garaiera handiagotuz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Pelin tavoitteena on tuhota kaikki rakennukset ja edetä seuraavalle tasolle. Kukin taso on edellistä vaikeampi; lentokone on nopeampi ja rakennukset ovat korkeampia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le but du jeu est de détruire tous les bâtiments pour atteindre le niveau suivant. Chaque niveau devient plus difficile en augmentant la vitesse de l'avion et la hauteur des bâtiments.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O obxectivo do xogo consiste en destruír os edificios e avanzar ao seguinte nivel. Cada novo nivel resultará máis difícil, pois aumentará a velocidade do avión, así como a altura dos edificios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A játék célja, hogy minden épületet elpusztítsunk, mielőtt továbbléphetnénk a következő szintre. Minden szint egyre nehezedik azzal, hogy a repülő sebessége növekszik, az épületek magassága pedig nő.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Tujuan permainan ini adalah untuk meledakkan semua bangunan dan berlanjut ke level selanjutnya. Setiap level agak sedikit susah dengan meningkatnya kecepatan pada pesawat dan tingginya bangunan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Lo scopo del gioco è di distruggere tutti gli edifici e raggiungere il livello successivo. Ogni livello è un po' più difficile perché aumenta la pendenza del piano e l'altezza degli edifici. </p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">게임 목표는 모든 건물을 파괴하고 다음 단계로 진행하는 것입니다. 각각 단계별로 비행기가 빨라지고 건물이 높아집니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Dat Speel is, Du rietst all Hüüs daal un kummst so na de nakamen Speelstoop. Elkeen Stoop is sworer; de Fleger fliggt gauer un de Hüüs sünd höger.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het doel van het spel is om alle gebouwen te vernietigen en verder te gaan naar het volgende niveau. Elk niveau wordt een beetje moeilijker door de snelheid van het vliegtuig te verhogen en de hoogte van de gebouwen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Målet med spelet er å bomba alle bygningane for å komma vidare til neste brett. Kvart brett vert vanskelgare, med raskare fly og høgare bygningar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Celem gry jest zniszczenie wszystkich budynków i przejście do następnego poziomu. Każdy poziom staje się coraz trudniejszy poprzez zwiększanie szybkości płaszczyzny i wysokości budynków.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O objectivo do jogo é destruir todos os edifícios e avançar para o nível seguinte. Cada nível vai ficando mais difícil, aumentando a velocidade do avião e a altura dos edifícios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O objetivo do jogo é destruir todos os edifícios e passar ao nível seguinte. Cada nível vai ficando um pouco mais difícil ao aumentar a velocidade do avião e a altura dos edifícios.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Цель игры — разрушить все здания и продвинуться на следующий уровень. Очередной уровень сложнее предыдущего за счёт увеличения скорости самолёта и высоты зданий.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Cieľom hry je zničiť všetky budovy na postúpenie do ďalšej úrovne. Každá úroveň je o niečo ťažšia zvýšením rýchlosti lietadla a výškou budov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Cilj igre je uničiti vse zgradbe in tako preiti v naslednjo stopnjo. Vsaka stopnja je težja, saj se poveča hitrost letala in višina zgradb.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Циљ игре је уништити све зграде и прећи на следећи ниво. Сваки ниво је мало тежи од претходног, тиме што се повећава брзина авиона и висина зграда.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Cilj igre je uništiti sve zgrade i preći na sledeći nivo. Svaki nivo je malo teži od prethodnog, time što se povećava brzina aviona i visina zgrada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Циљ игре је уништити све зграде и прећи на следећи ниво. Сваки ниво је мало тежи од претходног, тиме што се повећава брзина авиона и висина зграда.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Cilj igre je uništiti sve zgrade i preći na sledeći nivo. Svaki nivo je malo teži od prethodnog, time što se povećava brzina aviona i visina zgrada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Spelets mål är att förstöra alla byggnader och gå vidare till nästa nivå. Varje nivå blir lite svårare genom att planets hastighet och byggnadernas höjd ökar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Oyunun amacı şehirdeki bütün binaları yıkmak ve bir sonraki seviyeye geçmektir. Her seviyede uçağın hızı ve binaların yüksekliği arttırılarak zorluk arttırılır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Метою гри є зруйнувати всі будинки і перейти на наступний рівень. З кожним рівнем гра стає складнішою, оскільки зростає швидкість літака і висота будинків.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe goal of the game is to destroy all the buildings and advance to the next level. Each level gets a bit harder by increasing the speed of the plane and the height of the buildings.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">游戏的目标是摧毁所有建筑物，达成目标后可以进入下一关。每过一关，轰炸机的速度和建筑物的高度都会比前一关有所提高，游戏的难度也因此越来越高。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">遊戲的目的是要催毀所有的建築物，並進到下一關。每一關難度會越來越高，建築物也會越來越高。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/applications/games/bomber/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=bomber</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=bomber</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=bomber&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/bomber/bomber.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <developer_name>The KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="bs">KDE zajednica</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Komunita KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="da">KDE-fællesskabet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">Die KDE-Gemeinschaft</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="el">Η Κοινότητα του KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en-GB">The KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">La comunidad KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="et">KDE kogukond</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eu">KDE komunitatea</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fi">KDE-yhteisö</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">La communauté KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">A comunidade de KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hu">A KDE közösség</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="id">Komunitas KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">La Comunità KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">KDE 커뮤니티</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nds">De KDE-Meenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">De KDE gemeenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nn">KDE-fellesskapet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Społeczność KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">A Comunidade do KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ru">Сообщество KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">KDE komunita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Skupnost KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr">заједница КДЕ‑а</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr-Latn">zajednica KDE‑a</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">заједница КДЕ‑а</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">zajednica KDE‑a</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">KDE-gemenskapen</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">KDE Topluluğu</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Спільнота KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxThe KDE Communityxx</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE 社区</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE 社群</developer_name>
  <provides>
    <binary>bomber</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="21.08.0" date="2021-08-12"/>
    <release version="21.04.3" date="2021-07-08"/>
    <release version="21.04.2" date="2021-06-10"/>
    <release version="21.04.1" date="2021-05-13"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">mild</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
